[Music]
[音乐]
this is Nick with logos by Nick comm and
我是尼克·康姆的标志尼克
in today's tutorial I'll be
在今天的教程中，我将
demonstrating how you can use the
演示如何使用
pattern along path function in Inkscape
Inkscape中的沿路径图案功能
to create some unique and interesting
为了创造一些独特而有趣的东西
designs and patterns and if you'd like
设计和图案，如果你想
to learn more about how Inkscape works
要详细了解Inkscape的工作原理，请执行以下操作
be sure to check out the Inkscape master
一定要查看Inkscape大师
class which is a collection of over 60
类，它是超过60个元素的集合
videos that I created where I go over
我制作的视频，我看了一遍
all of the different tools and features
所有不同的工具和功能
in Inkscape and I explain what they are
在Inkscape中，我解释了它们是什么
and demonstrate how they work we even
并演示它们是如何工作的，我们甚至
have a private community where I could
有一个私人社区，在那里我可以
personally help you out and answer any
亲自帮助你，回答你的任何问题
questions you have I'll put a link in
你有什么问题我会给你加个链接
the description of the video if you want
视频的描述(如果需要
to check that out so we're going to get
去检查一下，这样我们就能
started here in Inkscape the first thing
从Inkscape开始，第一件事
we want to do is just make sure we're
我们想要做的就是确保我们
all working with a similar page setup so
都使用类似的页面设置，因此
I'm going to go to view make sure you
我要去看一看，确保你
have custom selected and then we're go
选择定制，然后我们就可以开始了
to view zoom and zoom in at 1 to 1 and
以1：1的比例查看缩放和放大以及
then I want to open up the align and
然后我想打开Align和
distribute menu with this button up here
此按钮位于此处的分发菜单
we're gonna want last selected chosen
我们想要最后一个被选中
from this drop-down and then I'm going
从这个下拉列表中，然后我要
to open up the Edit objects colors
打开编辑对象颜色的步骤
gradients and Stroke menu with this
带有此选项的渐变和笔划菜单
button over here so if you notice here I
按钮在这里，所以如果你注意到这里我
have this shape selected and what I'm
选择了这个形状，我是什么
gonna do is I'm gonna use the pattern
我要做的就是用这个模式
along path function in Inkscape to take
沿路径函数在Inkscape中取
this stretch to take this shape and
伸展到这个形状，然后
stretch it out and repeat it around a
把它伸展开，绕着一圈重复
circle now you don't have to use this
现在圈起来，你不用用这个了
shape you can use whatever shape you'd
形状你可以用任何你想要的形状
like you could use a circle or a star
就像你可以用一个圆圈或一个星星
you can create some kind of custom shape
您可以创建某种自定义形状
and shape if you'd like but what I'm
如果你愿意，可以塑造我的样子
gonna do is I'm gonna grab the circles
我要做的就是抓住圆圈
and ellipses tool and I'm gonna hold
和省略号工具，我要拿着
ctrl and shift and I'm gonna click and
按住Ctrl和Shift，然后我将单击并
drag in the campus to create a perfectly
拖进校园，打造完美的校园
round circle like that and this is the
像这样的圆形，这就是
path that I want to make this shape
我想要做成这个形状的路径
follow along so I want to take copies of
请跟我来，所以我想复印一下
this shape and make it repeat going all
这个形状，并让它重复所有
along the edges of this circle right
沿着这个圆圈的边缘向右
here so what I'm gonna do first is I'm
在这里，我首先要做的是
just going to convert this to a path
只需将其转换为路径
I'll get a path object to path and
我将从Path获取一个Path对象，然后
that's no longer a a circle or ellipse
这不再是一个圆或椭圆
object it's now recognized as a regular
对象，它现在被识别为常规的
path and what I'm going to do is I'm
我要做的是我要
going to open up the the path the path
我要打开这条路，这条路
effects menu by going to path and
通过转到路径和效果菜单
clicking on path effects and what I'm
点击路径效果和我在做什么
gonna do is I'm gonna click plus over
我要做的就是点击加号
here to add a new path effect to this
在这里添加一个新的路径效果
circle and I'm gonna look for pattern
圆圈和我要寻找的模式
along path it should be about halfway
沿着这条路，它应该在半路上
through the list here pattern along path
沿着路径通过列表中的模式
click Add
单击添加
and what I want to do now is I want to
我现在想做的是我想要
click on the shape that I'd like to
点击我想要的形状
apply around the circle I'm gonna grab
围绕着我要抓住的圆圈申请
the select tool I'm gonna click on my
我要点击我的选择工具
shape right here like I said you can use
就在这里，就像我说的，你可以用
any shape you'd like you don't have to
任何你想要的形状，你都不需要
use this here I'm gonna right click this
在这里用我要右击这个
and go to copy and then I'm gonna click
然后转到复制，然后我将点击
on this circle and over here in the
在这个圆圈上，在这里
pattern along path menu I'm gonna choose
我要选择沿着路径的图案菜单
where it says pattern copies i'm gonna
上面写着图案复印件我要
choose repeated stretched and i'm gonna
选择重复伸展，我会
click on this button over here that says
点击这里的按钮，上面写着
link path on clipboard and if you notice
剪贴板上的链接路径，如果您注意到
it took this object and repeated it
它拿起这个物体，重复了一遍
around the edge of that circle right
就在那个圆圈的边上
here and now this this circle here is
此时此刻这个圆圈就是
linked to this original shape so as i
链接到此原始形状，因此我
add it this shape this will edit along
添加此形状，此形状将随之编辑
with it now let me zoom in let me zoom
现在让我放大，让我放大
in let me scale this down a little bit
让我稍微缩小一下
let me make that back to black again i'm
让我让它再次变回黑色，我是
gonna scale this down and you're gonna
把规模缩小，你就会
notice it scales down the size of the
请注意，它缩小了
pattern here as well you'll notice if i
这里的模式也是如此，你会注意到如果我
make this smaller there's now more of
让它变得更小现在有更多
these shapes in here because the smaller
这些形状在这里是因为较小的
size means more of these shapes can fit
尺寸意味着可以容纳更多这样的形状
within this circle now it works the
在这个圈子里，它现在起作用了
other way as well if i make that larger
如果我把它做得更大，也有其他方法
now less of those shapes can fit within
现在，这些形状中可以容纳的更少了
that circle if you notice here start you
如果你注意到这个圆圈，你就会开始
get starting to get a little bit of a
开始变得有点
little bit of distortion in there so i'm
有一点扭曲，所以我
gonna make that a little smaller and
会让它变得更小一点
that's how the repeated stretch let me
这就是反复伸展让我
click on that again repeated stretch
再次点击该重复拉伸
that's how that works
这就是它的工作原理
now if you what you want to do is you
现在如果你想做的是你自己
can if you want you can add some spacing
可以，如果你想的话你可以加一些空格
between these where it says space and
在这上面写着空格和
then click on 5 and it adds 5 units of
然后点击5，它会添加5个单位
spacing between each object right there
每个对象之间的间距
if you notice there and that works on
如果你注意到了这一点，那就好了
the negative as well if i add negative 3
如果我加上负3，也是负的
you'll notice they start to overlap with
你会注意到它们开始重叠
each other each of those objects now let
现在每个对象都让彼此
me put that back to zero another thing
我把它归零还有一件事
you can do is nope there we go another
你能做的是，不，我们去另一个地方
thing you could do is you can use single
您可以做的是使用Single
stretched and if you choose single
拉伸，如果您选择单人
stretch what it's going to do is it's
拉长它要做的是它
gonna take this object and it's gonna
拿起这个物体，它就会
stretch it out all the way you learn all
把它延伸到你所学到的一切
the way around the perimeter of this
绕过这片区域的方式
path here now if you know you probably
如果你知道你很可能会走到这里
it's probably hard to tell what that is
可能很难分辨出那是什么
but you can if you if you really look
但你可以，如果你真的看起来
closely you can see it took this object
你可以近距离看到它带走了这个物体
and stretched it out like that so let me
像这样伸展开，所以让我
undo that let me put this back at
解开它，让我把它放回原处
repeated stretched and what
重复伸展和什么
you're done once you're happy with how
一旦你对你的方式感到满意，你就完了
this looks what you're wanting what you
这看起来就是你想要的
want to do is you want to finalize it
你想要做的就是最终敲定它
before you finalize it if you want you
在你定稿之前，如果你想
can remove the path and you it'll put it
可以移除路径，您可以将其放入
back to a circle let me undo that
回到原点，让我来解开它
or you can finalize it by going to path
或者您可以通过转到Path来最终确定它
object to path and now that's no longer
对象到路径，现在这不再是
a pattern along path object now this
现在，沿路径对象的图案
doesn't just work with circles you can
不仅适用于圆圈，你可以
do this with virtually any shape and
用几乎任何形状都可以这样做
I'll show you what I mean let me scale
我会告诉你我的意思，让我来衡量一下
that down put that out of the way I'm
那件事让我不再碍事了
gonna grab the Bezier pen over here and
我要拿起这里的贝塞尔钢笔
I'm gonna click to create a point I'm
我要点击创建一个点，我是
gonna hold ctrl bring the line across
按住Ctrl键将线对准对岸
the screen like this and then click to
这样的屏幕，然后点击
create another point and then press
创建另一个点，然后按
ENTER on the keyboard and I'm gonna grab
在键盘上输入，我要抓起
the Edit path by nodes tool and I'm
按结点编辑路径工具和我
gonna edit this line a little bit give
我要把这行编辑一下，给出
it a little bit of a curve that right
它有一点曲折，对吗？
there is what I'm looking for or
这就是我要找的或者
something like that and now I'm gonna
诸如此类的事情现在我要
again and once again I'm going to copy
我要一次又一次地复制
this right click copy I'm gonna click on
这是我要点击的右键复制
this path I'm gonna add I'm gonna come
我要加上的这条路，我会来的
back up here to the path effects menu
返回此处到路径效果菜单
click the plus to add a path effect
单击加号可添加路径效果
pattern a long path we want to use
设计一条我们想要使用的长路径
repeated stretched and I'm gonna go
反复伸展，我要走了
ahead and click link and if you notice
前进并点击链接，如果您注意到
here took the object and it stretched it
这里拿着物体，它把它拉长了
a lot and it repeated that along that
有很多，而且还在不断重复
path but it took on the properties of
路径，但它具有以下属性
the line that we drew where it had a
我们画的那条线是在
one-point stroke in no fill color so I'm
没有填充颜色的单点笔触，所以我
gonna give that a fill color and I'm
我会给它一个填充色，然后我
gonna get rid of the outline otherwise
否则我会去掉提纲的
known as the stroke by holding shift and
通过按住Shift键和
clicking on the X right there and that
点击那里的X，然后
right there it took this pattern and it
就在那里，它采用了这个模式，然后它
applied it along this path here now
现在沿着这条路在这里应用
another thing you can do with this is
您可以用它做的另一件事是
you can use this to create like kind of
你可以用它来创建一种
like a wreath let me show you what I
就像一个花环，让我向你展示我
mean here I'm gonna grab the circles and
意思是在这里我要抓住圆圈
ellipses tool I'm gonna hold ctrl and
省略号工具我要按住Ctrl键和
shift to create a circle like that let
按Shift键可创建这样的圆圈
me bring the opacity down a little bit
我把不透明度降低了一点
grab the Select tool duplicate that by
抓取选择工具通过以下方式复制
hitting ctrl D and hold ctrl move this
按下Ctrl D并按住Ctrl移动此按钮
over to the right click and drag over
向右单击并拖动
both of those and go to path
这两个都是去PATH
intersection and this shape right here
交叉口和这里的这个形状
is what we're looking for I'm gonna
就是我们要找的东西我要
right click that and go to copy and now
右键单击该选项，然后转到复制，然后立即
I'm going to create another circle I'm
我要创造另一个圈子我要
going to hold ctrl and shift click and
按住Ctrl键和Shift键并单击
drag click and drag to create a circle
拖动、单击并拖动以创建圆
convert that to a path by going to path
通过转到路径将其转换为路径
object to path
对象到路径
and now I will add a path effect to this
现在我将在此基础上添加路径效果
again once again pattern along path I'm
再一次沿着我的路走下去
gonna choose repeated stretched and I'm
我会选择重复伸展，而我
going to go ahead and link it and if you
我将继续链接它，如果您
notice here it's taking this object and
注意这里它把这个物体
linking it it's it's repeating it around
把它联系起来，它在重复它
the outside of that circle so let me
那个圆圈的外面，所以让我
grab the Select tool I want to click on
抓起我想要点击的选择工具
this object click on it again to get the
此对象再次单击它以获取
rotation handles I'm just gonna hold
旋转手柄我只需要握住
ctrl and rotate this to the right a
按Ctrl键并将其向右旋转a
couple of times like that and if you
像这样的几次，如果你
notice here on the left side we're
请注意，在左侧，我们
starting to get what appears to be kind
开始得到看似友善的东西
of like this this could be kind of like
就像这样，这可能是一种
a reef like a of a wreath of leaves let
像树叶花环一样的礁石让
me scale this down to show you I'm gonna
我缩小规模来向你展示我会
add some spacing in there let me click
在里面加一些空格，让我点击
on the on the on the path effect here
在这里的路径效应
I'm gonna add some spacing in there
我要在里面加一些空格
woops messed something up there there we
伍普斯在那里搞砸了一些东西我们
go let's add to see how that looks maybe
去吧，让我们添加一下，看看它看起来怎么样
a little less than that maybe a little
比这还少一点，可能有一点
more let me rotate this around a little
更多，让我把这个旋转一下
bit and as you rotate it it changes the
位，当您旋转它时，它会改变
position as you can see there now I like
你现在可以看到的位置，我喜欢
how that looks right there I'm gonna
它看起来怎么样，我要
finalize that by clicking on it and
通过点击它来完成它，然后
going to path object to path and I'm
要将对象路径到路径，而我
going to create another circle inside of
将在内部创建另一个圆
there let me grab the circles and
好了，让我抓住圆圈
ellipses tool hold ctrl and shift click
省略号工具按住Ctrl键和Shift键并单击
and drag to create a slightly smaller
并拖动以创建稍小的
circle than this one Center it up inside
比这个更圆，居中对齐
of here click and drag over both of
在此处单击并拖动到两个
those and Center them up on the center
把它们放在中心位置
on the vertical and horizontal axis path
关于垂直轴路径和水平轴路径
object to path and now I'll click on
对象到路径，现在我将单击
this I want these leaves to go the
这个我想让这些树叶
opposite way the opposite direction of
相反的方向相反的方向
these so I'm just gonna flip this one
这些，所以我要把这个翻过来
horizontally I'll click on this button
在水平方向上，我将点击此按钮
up here that says flip selected objects
上面写着翻转选定的对象
horizontally right click that go to copy
在水平方向上右键单击转到复制
click on this path and make that a
单击此路径并将其设置为
little bit bigger and once again I will
再大一点，我会再一次
add a path effect same way as I did with
添加路径效果的方法与添加路径效果的方法相同
the other objects repeated stretched
其他物体重复拉伸
link it and two point spacing like we
像我们这样把它和两个点间距连接起来
did before we make that a little bigger
在我们把它做得更大之前
I think I used less spacing than that
我想我用的空格比那个少
let me bring that down a little bit
让我把它降低一点。
okay that looks pretty good right about
好的，看起来很不错。
there and I will go I will finalize that
好了，我要走了，我要把它敲定。
by going to path object to path and now
通过转到路径对象到路径，现在
what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna break
我要做的是我要打破
this apart so what this is all
撇开这个不谈，这一切都是什么
individual pieces I'll go to path break
单件作品，我要去小路休息
apart and let me get rid of some of
分开，让我去掉一些
these extras in here I want to just keep
我想把这些多余的东西留在这里
the left side here so let me get rid of
左边在这里，所以让我去掉
these press Delete on the keyboard to
这些按钮按键盘上的Delete键以
thing over here path break apart let me
这里的东西让我分崩离析
get rid of these extras over here like I
像我一样把这些临时演员赶走
said I'm just keeping the left hand side
说我只是保持左手边
a little accent piece or a wreath like
像这样的小花环或花环
that let me bring the opacity to this up
这让我把不透明带到了这里
let me group it together by clicking the
让我将其分组，方法是单击
group selected objects button and now I
对选定对象进行分组按钮，现在我
can duplicate that by hitting ctrl D
可以通过按Ctrl D键来复制
hold ctrl click and drag this off to the
按住Ctrl键并单击并将其拖到
right flip this horizontally and there
向右水平翻转这个，就在那里
you go now you can put some kind of
你现在走吧，你可以放一些
design in the middle here you can create
中间的设计，你可以在这里创造
some kind of like little law maybe like
一些类似的小法律，也许像
an award graphic or some kind of logo
颁奖图形或某种标志
with these sorts of decorations on it
上面有这样的装饰品
but I think that should do it for this
但我认为这应该可以解决这个问题
video that take and go about using the
这些视频可以使用
pattern along path effects with Inkscape
使用Inkscape沿路径图案效果
if you have any questions let me know
如果你有任何问题，请告诉我
and as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]